It's the only time the mask full of
That's when I breathe
When the static becomes on
I'm honey on your sins
Then I'm on your tongue
So what you running from baby
Wake up. I had a good dreams and stuff. I woke up in a good mood. Actually, I still need to be careful not to like open my legs
Oh my gosh
Anyway, what are these people? There's such losers. Um, I'm just referring to bronze chicken and uh,
you know
It the clown or whatever her name is
Oh christine
But yeah, pretty lame. I mean, it's like what she attacked me for she said cuz I wanted to buy gifts for my nieces and nephews
That's what that's your attack and then his attack was that my my coat has lint on it
It's actually not lint. It's probably cat hair and I do wash it think all the time
But it's like, you know, it gets covered in cat hair instantly
But they have they just like oh, I'm dirty. Oh get a job
Okay, so I probably made more last month on YouTube than Christine did made a nursing, right?
Plus, you know
Minus like the blood money for like, you know unaliving baby goats, right Christine?
Yeah, so I know it's silly
I mean they want to say that shit about me and it's like that's I mean
That's all they had. Oh, and she's like, oh and you're broke go get a job. You're a grifter. I mean, it's like these are just like I
Mean is there like a hurt like hurt
Person inside of there like what's wrong with them? Really? I mean it's like and then I fight back like you know
Oh, you see that caddy holds up. What about Rudy? What do you have to say about Rudy? You keep Rudy's name out of your mouth
We used to give her yeah, baby goats
So we can play her song. I don't think she likes her song. I mean, it's like a good song, right?
I mean everyone loves this song right? It's one of my classics
It's called Christine
It's like, actually, you know why people like it?
Because it's only a minute long.
But here, let's be real quick.
There once was a nurse named Christine
with a frown sharper than her hygiene.
She blocked half the chat and their cousins with that
like a digital grumpy machine.
She'd schooled and she'd glare and she'd
I like that, I like that.
Would you like to kiss me?
Would you like to kiss?
Oh, oh.
Oh, you love to kiss me.
Oh, you do.
Oh, I love you too, baby.
Oh, you're dead.
Hey, Paul, how are you?
Mmm.
I love you.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
i'm trying to do a show here come on you're kissing me oh you're kissing me oh you're kissing
me oh my god oh okay here we go
what guys are you ready for the new premiere i have a new video premiere for you
I hope you guys like my music because brand new video premiere. Hope you like it
Do not turn your head pilgrim
The air is thick with omens and hungry eyes
Keep your heart beat steady as a drum in the underhaul
No flinch, no tremor
For bread it is a door that tastes of panic
Chain reactions coy like serpents around your ankles
and crawl
new accessory hi what do you do with my love she just jumped on me she like hid
my eyes so hard too oh my god I look like shit I'm sorry I know I do but I
just like I'm so slow it's like they're making fun of me sick I mean who's gonna
make fun of someone for being sick yeah this cat is so cute look at this cat so
See, some people just don't know these things.
Very glitchy.
Very glitchy, yeah.
of a pixel skin, every wink on cam is a quiet sin
close to christmas dream and a hood, no face
dropping big donuts like a hidden run, grace type
fan that one then disappears like a glitch in the feed
or a god in the wires, we roast each other like chestnut shard
laugh too loud cause it's all too hard, but under all the memes
and the curse of a laser, the cults of souls that refuse to fade
you can say one night when the clock hits three
the broke and the blocked, they'll all break free
and somewhere in the code of this crooked stream
there's an alex return like a hidden thing
I'm like where's my summer hit?
Floody diamond anthem, I'm so mad about it
I said look around bro, the sun's long gone
We turned your beach track into a hexed up song
Now it's Floody diamond song full of a cursed white street
Standing with a grill and ate a way slate beat
Same petty lyrics just cold to remain red, cocked in my hand
Green light on my screen
Congratulations Otto
Your thirsty June jam caught frostbite
So you can get like dollar fries on the app,
like they're like a dollar something for large fries.
And then dollar coffee and stuff.
So if you know how to like work the app,
you can get pretty good deals.
And then you get free food on it too.
So you can like, when you don't have anything,
you could like get food.
I want to get more coffee.
They always give me the small cup.
I always order the large.
They can be the small cup of coffee.
I know I do have a...
a flirty diamond auto song but they have it anymore. I mean I have it but it's
like it's like easy to find. Unless it's called like flirty, let me check. Or auto.
Okay, and that's the name flirty
That's the name auto
You need to go back and look
What I call it
Hi, babe. Oh
Excuse me. Oh my gosh
Oh it goes, do not hold, do not turn your head pilgrim.
The air is sick with omens and hungry eyes.
Keep your heart beat steady as a drum in the underhaul.
No flinch, no tremor for predators adore the taste of panic.
Chain reactions coil like serpents around your ankles the faction waits in shadow
Listening judging wondering if you will rise like a comet or fold like a forgotten prayer
Will you leap will you burn or will you finally face the tear that's been sidelined you walk through the dark?
In a good song
My favorites ever wrote uh-oh
I think Lenore wants to go on to the covers and make their bed, so I'm just gonna end the stream, but I love you
Thank you for me here. Hope you enjoyed that premiere. Hey, I'm gonna do it again, so